Hello friends, today we are discussing the stock
ICICI Lord General Insurance Company.
I have put its daily chart here.
Within its daily chart, I have put an
indicator called 20 and 200
exponential moving averages. So, here on the
screen, you can see that this
red line is my 20-day
exponential moving average and its
value is coming out to be around
1764, that is, 1764. And the
black line inside it, its value is coming out to be
around 1842. And
on the screen, you can see that the current price of this stock is
trading between both the moving averages. So, the
level of the current price of the stock is coming out to be
around 1825. I have
indicated this in yellow color. So, here
you can see that this stock
was below both its moving averages in March.  At the
beginning of the month,
it again crossed above the 20-day moving average
and took support here by forming two red candles
and
this stock has come back upwards. So now you have to do one thing
that if there is any decline in this stock
again and in that decline,
if you find the stock around the 20-day moving average of
1764, then you
can buy it by taking a stop loss on the 20-day moving average
and if this stock closes above the 200-day
moving average of 1842,
then
you can buy it by taking a stop loss on the 200-day EM of 1842
and
in the coming days, this stock will generate a good return from here. So
friends, this was my today's
analysis of ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company. So, how did you like today's video, let
me know by commenting.  Let me know and thank you
very much for watching today's video.